[{"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "In Jackass: The Movie, when Johnny Knoxville is dressed as the old man and he is shoplifting he says that he was once the lover of which one of these people?", "correct_answer": "Lon Cheney", "incorrect_answers": ["Cary Grant", "Greta Garbo", "Anne Francis"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "In the animated family movie Meet the Robinsons, what color were the gym teachers shorts?", "correct_answer": "green", "incorrect_answers": ["red", "blue", "pink"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "What does Chunks family bring to the beach in the film The Goonies, as the rescue party arrives to claim all of the gang?", "correct_answer": "Pizza", "incorrect_answers": ["Cookies", "McDonalds", "Donuts"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "The Great Pavement, a hidden, unknown to most tourists and seldom-displayed treasure, is located in which building in London?", "correct_answer": "Westminster Abbey", "incorrect_answers": ["Buckingham Palace", "Tate Gallery", "St Jamess Palace"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "Which of these is a computer for bulk data processing?", "correct_answer": "Mainframe", "incorrect_answers": ["A-frame", "Body-on-frame", "Window-frame"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "What British naturalist published the first major scientific study on facial communication in 1872?", "correct_answer": "Charles Darwin", "incorrect_answers": ["Leonardo Da Vinci", "Alfred Brehm", "James Edward Smith"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "Which of these colors has the following connotations: warning, fall, warmth, hope, summer, electricity?", "correct_answer": "Yellow", "incorrect_answers": ["Red", "Blue", "White"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "In the year 632, he succeeded Mohamed and became the First Caliph.", "correct_answer": "Abu Bakr", "incorrect_answers": ["Tahallah", "Abu Qahafa", "al-Zubahr"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "What does the drunk say when entering the aliens\u2019 spaceship at the end of the 1996 movie Independence Day?", "correct_answer": "Im Back!", "incorrect_answers": ["Die!", "Nothing", "Rot In Hell!"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "After reading the following, what will a doctor conclude? Pt presents 3 d S/P TURP, with c/o HA x 2 d.", "correct_answer": "The patient has a headache.", "incorrect_answers": ["The patient recently had abdominal surgery.", "The patient has no current complaints.", "The patient is female."]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "Which time zone encompasses the least number of the continuous 48 United States?", "correct_answer": "Pacific", "incorrect_answers": ["Eastern", "Central", "Mountain"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "In medicine, which of these brain disorders does the term prosopagnosia refer to?", "correct_answer": "The Inability to recognize faces", "incorrect_answers": ["The inability to express emotions", "Misinterpretation of basic human expressions", "Total indifference to others expressions"]}]